JASON SIMPSON

Experienced automotive technician with a strong track record for effective team leadership and training. Specialized knowledge of adaptive equipment installation and maintenance and a d ept at u sing co m p uter system s to d i agn ose co m pl ex fau Its. 5 u perb customer service skills with a talent for managing client relationships.

234 Address Boulevard, Louisville. KY 43234 j.simpson@myemail.com (987) 789-9876

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

SENIOR AUTOMOTIVE TECHNICIAN

Su reSa le, Louisville, KY July 2018 - Present

AUTOMOTIVE TECHNICIAN

Superior Vans and Mobility, Louisville, KT July 2013-July 2018

- Use computer diagnostic systems to detect mechanical problems in vehiclesand assess their roadworthiness, achieving a 99.8% accuracy rating in 2020
- Train an average of 10 new hires and student interns per year to improve their knowledge of government regulations
- Mentor and monitor a team of 20 mobile technicians, acting as an escalation point for complex diagnostic issues
- Explain and promote the company's verification process to large dealerships, securing an 89% contract renewal rate over two years
- Installed adaptive equipment and driving aids to improve vehicle accessibility for people with limited mobility and wheelchair users
- Established a quick customer rapport and managed relationships carefully, securing a 78% repeat custom rate
- Performed routine maintenance on adaptive technologies to reduce fault development by an average of 23% per year
- Leveraged computerized diagnostic tools to detect problems and recommend practical solutions

EDUCATION

Associate of Applied Science in Automotive Technology

Bluegrass Community And Technical College, Lexington, KY September 2011 - June 2013

KEY SKILLS

- · Computer diagnostics
- · Routine maintenance
- Adaptive equipment
- Customer service
- · Leadership and mentoring
- ♦ Wri tten and ve rba I com m u n i cat io n

CERTIFICATIONS

 Brake Repair Certification, August 2013